Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Volleyball photos
    - 1981
      - Western Michigan 9/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Wayne State 11/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1982
      - Minnesota 9/24/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Illinois 10/15/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1983
      - Georgia 9/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Indiana 10/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1984
      - Bowling Green, 9//1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Illinois-Chicago Circle 9/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Miami (OH) 10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Eastern Michigan 11/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1985
      - Eastern Michigan 9/17/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Michigan State 10/22/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1986
      - Northwood 9/23/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Central Michigan 11/11/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1987
      - Bowling Green 9/22/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1988
      - Eastern Michigan 9/13/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Indiana 9/30/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1989
      - Michigan State 9/20/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Ohio State 10/07/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1990
      - Akron 9/05/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Eastern Michigan 9/11/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Indiana 9/28/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Michigan State 11/14/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Wisconsin 11/23/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1991
      - Indiana 10/05/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Michigan State 10/09/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Illinois 10/25/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1992
      - Indiana 9/25/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Iowa 10/16/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Michigan State 10/28/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Wisconsin 10/30/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Penn State 11/06/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1993
      - Illinois State 9/01/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Stanford 9/03/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Michigan State 9/22/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Notre Dame 10/12/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Ohio State 10/22/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
      - Purdue 11/12/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 45)
    - 1994
      - Eastern Michigan 9/07/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Pittsburgh 9/10/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Wisconsin 11/25/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Northwestern 11/26/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 1995
      - UCLA 9/08/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Purdue 9/22/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - MSU 9/27/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Minnesota 10/13/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Wisconsin 10/14/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 1996
      - Georgia 9/07/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Notre Dame 9/20/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Wisconsin 10/11/1996 (Box 46)
      - Indiana 10/25/1996 (Box 46)
      - OSU 11/16/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Illinois 11/29/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 1997
      - Florida St. 09/05/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Montana 9/06/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Penn St., 10/17 1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Iowa 11/14/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Purdue 11/29/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 1998
      - North Carolina 9/11/1998 (Box 46)
      - MSU 10/07/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Minnesota 10/09/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Iowa 10/24/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 1999
      - Notre Dame 4/14/1999 (Box 46)
      - Alumni 8/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Pepperdine 9/10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Arkansas 9/11/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - OSU 9/24/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Penn St. 9/5/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Northwestern 10/16/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Illinois 11/06/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Indiana 11/20/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - MSU 11/24/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
    - 2000
      - Toledo 9/28/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Notre Dame, 10/18/200, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Purdue 11/03/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
      - Wisconsin 11/24/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 46)
  - U-M Softball photos
    - 1978
      - Detroit 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Bowling Green 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1979
      - Jackson Community College 4/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Lansing 4/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1980
      - Albion 4/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Grand Valley 4/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1981
      - Detroit 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Michigan State 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1982
      - Big Ten Tournament 4/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Eastern Michigan 4/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Bowling Green 5/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Kent State 5/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1983
      - Iowa 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Wayne State 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Ohio State 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Tournament 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1984
      - Indiana 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Western Michigan 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Bowling Green 5/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Minnesota 5/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1985
      - Indiana 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Iowa 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Toledo 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1986
      - Minnesota 4/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Northwestern 5/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Michigan State 5/07/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1987
      - Indiana 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Toledo 4/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Iowa 5/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1988
      - Alumni 11/01/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Western Michigan 4/04/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Northwestern 4/30/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Minnesota 5/07/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/11/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1989
      - Indiana 4/15/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Toledo 4/19/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Iowa 4/29/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1990
      - Minnesota 4/07/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Northwestern 4/20/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Western Michigan 4/24/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1991
      - Michigan Invitational Tournament 4/06/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Iowa 4/13/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1992
      - NSK Wolverine Classic, Fall/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Northwestern 4/04/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Central Michigan 4/22/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
      - Ohio State 5/01/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 47)
    - 1993
      - Alumni game, Dedication of Alumni Field 9/13/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Michigan State 4/13/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Penn State 5/01/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Toledo 5/12/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA-Regional 5/22/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1994
      - [unknown] 4/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1995
      - DePaul 5/19/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1996
      - Iowa 3/30/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Northwestern 4/06/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Toledo 4/11/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - OSU 4/27/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Big Ten Tournament, Minnesota and Indiana 5/10/1996-5/11/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - South Carolina, NCAA Regional 5/19/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Wayne St. 10/12/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1997
      - Wisconsin 3/29/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - CMU 4/16/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Minnesota, 4/191997-4/20/1997 x (Box 48)
      - MSU 4/22/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Indiana 4/26/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regional, CMU 5/16/1997, 5/18/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regional, Cleveland St. 5/17/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1998
      - OSU 4/04/1998-4/05/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Western Michigan 4/16/1998 (Box 48)
      - Northwestern 4/18/1998-4/19/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Iowa 4/25/1998-4/26/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Big Ten Tournament, Indiana 5/08/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regionals 5/17/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 1999
      - Minnesota 4/10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - MSU 4/21/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Wisconsin 5/01/1999-5/02/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Big ten Tournament, Iowa 5/14/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - Big Ten Tournament 5/15/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regional, Florida Atlantic 5/20/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
    - 2000
      - Bowling Green 4/19/2000 (Box 48)
      - Stanford 5/18/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regional, DePaul 5/20/2000 (Box 48)
      - NCAA Regional, University of Illinois-Chicago 5/21/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 48)
  - U-M Women's Soccer photos
    - 1994
      - Wisconsin-Green Bay 9/03/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Northern Illinois 9/05/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1995
      - Buffalo 9/17/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Creighton 08/20/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Butler 10/22/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1996
      - California-Berkeley,9/20/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Indiana 9/29/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Minnesota 10/13/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Dayton 10/27/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Valparaiso 11/13/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1997
      - Eastern Michigan 9/14/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - OSU 9/21/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Northwestern 9/28/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - MSU 10/26/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Detroit 9/13/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1999
      - Detroit 9/13/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Penn St. 9/25/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Iowa 10/02/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1999
      - Utah. 9/12/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Illinois 9/24/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Purdue 10/03/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Wright St. 11/03/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 2000
      - Minnesota 9/28/2000, negatives (Box 49)
      - Ohio State 10/15/2000, negatives (Box 49)
  - U-M Men's Soccer photos
    - 2000
      - Michigan State 10/15/2000 (Box 49)
  - U-M Field Hockey photos
    - 1979
      - Central Michigan 9/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1980
      - Eastern Michigan 10/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1981
      - Michigan State 9/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Central Michigan 9/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Bowling Green 10/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1982
      - St. Louis 9/17/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Albion 9/21/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Iowa 10/15/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Old Dominion 10/28/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1983
      - Northwestern 9/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Iowa 10/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1984
      - Toledo 10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Notre Dame 10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Iowa 11/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1985
      - Central Michigan 9/17/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Northwestern 10/11/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1986
      - Ohio 9/05/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Toledo 9/09/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1987
      - Notre Dame 9/12/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Miami 9/13/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1988
      - Ohio University 9/25/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1989
      - Ohio 9/25/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
      - Boston C. 10/15/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 49)
    - 1990
      - Iowa 10/26/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Northern Illinois 10/28/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1991
      - Central Michigan 9/16/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Michigan State 10/13/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1992
      - Miami 9/29/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Penn State 10/09/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Kent State 10/31/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1994
      - Eastern Michigan 9/07/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Ball State 10/11/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Villanova 10/19/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1995
      - Delaware 9/08/1995 (Box 50)
      - Penn St. 10/06/1995 (Box 50)
      - OSU 10/08/1995 (Box 50)
    - 1996
      - Boston College 9/08/1996 (Box 50)
      - Central Michigan 10/15/1996 (Box 50)
      - Iowa 11/03/1996 (Box 50)
    - 1997
      - North Carolina 9/06/1997 (Box 50)
      - Penn St. 10/24/1997 (Box 50)
      - MSU, 112.1997 (Box 50)
    - 1998
      - Ball State 9/01/1998 (Box 50)
      - Stanford 9/13/1998 (Box 50)
      - MSU 9/24/1998 (Box 50)
      - Penn St. 10/11/1998 (Box 50)
      - Northwestern 10/30/1998 (Box 50)
    - 1999
      - Northeastern 9/05/1999 (Box 50)
      - California 9/26/1999 (Box 50)
      - MSU 10/17/1999 (Box 50)
      - Penn St. 10/29/1999 (Box 50)
      - OSU 10/31/1999 (Box 50)
      - Wright St. 11/10/1999 (Box 50)
    - 2000
      - Rutgers 9/10/2000, negatives (Box 50)
      - Miami, 9/19/200, negatives (Box 50)
      - Ohio State 9/24/2000, negatives (Box 50)
      - Northwestern 10/06/2000, negatives (Box 50)
      - Central Michigan, 10/07/200, negatives (Box 50)
      - Michigan State 11/05/2000, negatives (Box 50)
      - Award Dinner 11/2000, negatives (Box 50)
  - U-M Track (Men's/Women's) photos
    - 1975
      - Michigan Relays 1/1975, negatives (Box 50)
      - Bowling Green, Notre Dame 2/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Chicago Track Club 5/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1976
      - Bowling Green, Notre Dame 1/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1977
      - Central Collegiate Championships 2/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Wolverine Invitational 2/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Big Ten Meet 3/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1978
      - Michigan Relays 1/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Michigan State 2/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Wolverine Invitational 2/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Wolverine Invitational 5/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1979
      - Central Michigan 2/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Wolverine Invitational 2/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Ann Arbor Relays 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
      - Big Ten Championships 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 50)
    - 1980
      - Michigan Relays 1/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Central Collegiate 2/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Central Michigan 2/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Chicago Track Club 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1981
      - Michigan Relays 1/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Western Michigan 1/1981 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Central Collegiate 2/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Ferris State 2/1981 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Central Michigan 4/1981 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Chicago 5/1981 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1982
      - Michigan Relays 1/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Lady Invitational 2/1982 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Invitational 2/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Chicago Track Club 5/1982 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1983
      - Michigan Relays 1/1983 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan Relays 1/1983 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan State 2/1983 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Nike 2/1983 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Red Simmons Invitational 4/1983 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1984
      - Michigan Relay 1/1984 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan Relay 1/1984 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Invitational 2/1984 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Big Tens 3/1984 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Red Simmons Invitational 4/1984 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Chicago 5/12/1984 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1985
      - Michigan Relays 1/1985 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan Relays 1/1985 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Central Collegiate 2/1985 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Open 2/1985 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Ann Arbor Relays 5/1985 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1986
      - Michigan Relays 1/1986 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan Relays 1/1986 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Men's & Women's track meet 2/1986 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Diamond Invitational 5/1986 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Len Paddock Invitational 5/1986 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Red Simmons Meet 5/1986 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1987
      - Intra-squad track meet 12/1986 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Open 2/1987 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Big Tens 3/1987 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Men's track 3/1987 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Len Padduck Invitational 5/1987 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1988
      - Michigan Relays 1/16/1988 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Michigan Relays 1/23/1988 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Big Tens 5/21-22/1988 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1989
      - Michigan Relays-prelims 1/21/1989 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
      - Wolverine Open 1/21/1989 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 51)
    - 1990
      - Michigan Relays 1/20/1990 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Red Simmons Invitational 2/10/1990 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1991
      - Intrasquad 12/15/1990 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Michigan Relays 1/19/1991 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Red Simmons 2/09/1991 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Paddock Invitational 5/11/1991 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1992
      - Ohio State, Michigan State 1/25/1992 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Red Simmons Invitational 2/15/1992 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Paddock Invitational 5/16/1992 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1993
      - Michigan Relays 1/16/1993 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Silverston Invitational 2/27/1993 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Paddock Invitational 5/15/1993 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1994
      - Red Simmons Invitational 1/22/1994 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Michigan Relays 1/29/1994 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1995
      - Indiana 1/14/1995 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Red Simmons 1/21/1995 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Central Collegiate 2/11/1995 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Big Tens 2/25-26/1995 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1996
      - Red Simmons Invitational, (W) 1/20/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Michigan Invitational? 1/27/1996 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1997
      - MSU, Indiana 1/11/1997 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - 3/01/1997 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Phil Diamond Invitational 5/10/1997 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Len Paddock 5/17/1997 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1998
      - Michigan Open 1/10/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Red Simmons Invitational 1/24/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Central Collegiate 2/14/1998 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - 5/08/1998 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Len Paddock Invitational 5/15/1998-5/16/1998 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1999
      - Red Simmons Invitational 1/23/1999 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Phil Diamond Invitational 5/08/1999-5/09/1999 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Len Paddock 5/15/1999-5/16/1999 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 2000
      - Silverston 2/13/2000 (M&W) (Box 52)
  - U-M Cross-Country (Men's/Women's) photos
    - 1980
      - Bowling Green 9/1980 (W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
      - Michigan State 10/1980 (M), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1985
      - Michigan Invitational 10/1985 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1989
      - Michigan Invitational 10/14/1989 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1991
      - Michigan Invitational 10/05/1991 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)
    - 1992
      - Michigan Open 9/11/1992 (M&W), negatives, contact sheets (Box 52)